

Emre Topcu <u>info.etopcu@gmail.com</u> Üsküdar, İstanbul, Turkey

Phone Number: +90 505 726 72 65 www.linkedin.com/in/emre-topcu04/

PROFILE

A 20-year-old Computer Science Engineering student at Akdeniz University, proficient in Java, Python, Solidity, Kotlin, and JavaScript. Fluent in English and interested in Data Science, Machine Learning, and Front-End Development. Known for being easy to get along with and a hard worker, with a strong aspiration to pursue a career in academia.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Akdeniz University | Antalya, Turkey

2022 - Present

Faculty of Engineering

B.Sc, Computer Science Engineering (English)

Expected Rank: 3rd among the same year graduate students

Current CGPA: 3.87/4.0

WORK EXPERIENCE

GTSFly | Antalya, Turkey

2024 - 2024

Intern

• During my internship at GTSFly, a Germany-based firm with a development team in Antalya, I worked on the admin page of their platform. Our primary focus was on building key components using the Vue.js framework. This experience allowed me to deepen my skills in front-end development and contribute to a significant project.

SOCIAL ACTIVITIES & VOLUNTEERING

Best Buddies | Istanbul, Turkey

2018 - 2021

Attendant

• We worked as a participant at the Best Buddies organization, where we had the opportunity to engage with individuals who have Down syndrome and developed meaningful friendships with them.

Google Student Developer Club Akdeniz | Antalya, Turkey

2022 - 2022

Attendant

• I am an enthusiastic member of the GDSC Akdeniz society and actively participate in their activities.

IEEE Akdeniz Student Branch | Antalya, Turkey

2023 - 2023

Blockchain Community - Chair

• I am an administrative board member of the IEEE Akdeniz Student Branch where we have actively 2600+ members. Other than that, I am currently the chair of the Blockchain Community where we give webinars, seminars, and lectures to give students the love of Blockchain technology while informing them.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- IEEE Akdeniz Student Branch Chair of Blockchain
- İş Hayatı 101 Participant (Prestigious program that's held by ASELSAN)
- Savunma Sanayi 101 Participant (Prestigious program that's held by the Ministry Of Defence)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Hard Skills: Proficient in Java, Python, JavaScript, HTML,CSS, Kotlin as programming languages. Proficient in Pandas, NumPy, Matploblib and Seaborn as Libraries. Proficient in Vue.js as framework. Proficient in Git as version control systems. Proficient in Data Structures and Algorithms.

Soft Skills: Team Leadership, Organization Skills, Event Planning, Leadership, Communication, Problem Solving, Analytical Skills

Languages: English (C1), German (A2)